RG 097, Connecticut Commission on the Arts
Connecticut State Library
Commission on the Arts records
1962-1978
Connecticut State Library
Connecticut Commission on the Arts
65 cubic feet
The Commission was responsible for encouraging “participation in, and promotion, development, acceptance and appreciation of” the cultural resources of the state. Its work fell generally into five categories: Programs, Program Development, Information Services, Technical Assistance and Grants. The seven main areas of work are in: Community Development, Dance, Education, Literature, Music, Theatre and Visual Arts.
RG097
1979-001
Historical Note
In 1963, a Commission on the Arts established by Special Act 106, to make a comprehensive survey of the state and report findings to the Governor by Jan. 1965. In 1965, the Connecticut General Assembly passed Public Act 579 creating the Connecticut Commission on the Arts, a public service agency responsible for encouraging “participation in, and promotion, development, acceptance and appreciation of” the cultural resources of the state. The agency was governed by an independent board of 25 commissioners appointed by the Governor, President of the Senate, and Speaker of the House. The Commission maintained a staff of administrative, fiscal, consultative, and field personnel. The Commission was placed under the Department of Education for administrative purposes only by the State Reorganization Act of 1978 and then in 1995 under the State Library for the same reason. The Commission’s work falls generally into five categories: Programs, Program Development, Information Services, Technical Assistance and Grants. The seven main areas of work are in: Community Development, Dance, Education, Literature, Music, Theatre and Visual Arts. On June 30, 2003 the Commission merged with other agencies to form the Commission on Arts, Tourism, Culture, History, and Film per Public Act 03-6.
Scope and Content
"300 Years of Connecticut Architecture" Exhibit materials, 1968-1974, were collected as part of a town by town state survey of architectural records made in 1968. It resulted in an exhibit that traced the development of Connecticut architecture from 1639 to 1974 and constitute a photographic history of Connecticut. The exhibit opened at the Wadsworth Athenaeum in 1971, and toured the state through 1974.
Dance materials, 1965-1977, include correspondence, clippings, programs, press releases, publications relating to the Commission's dance activities. In its 1965 report to the Governor and Legislature, the Temporary Commission on the Arts indicated that, in Connecticut, dance was the performing art needing greatest development. Since 1966 the permanent agency's support efforts in this field have fallen into three general categories: audience building, upgrading standards in schools of dance and companies, and bringing dance into closer contact with public education.
Project Create materials, 1967-1970, include press releases, clippings, correspondence, evaluations, and financial records dealing with the administration of the program. Between 1967 and 1970, Project Create brought arts-in-education programs to nine Connecticut elementary schools. Developed by the Commission, the project was funded and administered through Title III of the Elementary and Secondary Education Act, with a budget of $425,000 for the three year period. Project Create was designed to "break through the limitations of a rigidly academic, verbal tradition to show how the creative arts can stimulate the full learning, thinking and doing activities of children." Each school maintained an artist-in-residence who also brought visiting artists and performing groups to schools.
Artists-In-Schools Program materials consist mainly of school files relative to the program. The Artists-in-Schools program, funded by the National Endowment for the Arts, related the creative process of practicing artists to students in an educational setting.
Educational materials, 1967-1976, relate to the arts in Connecticut schools, including material relative to the Teacher's Project Assistance Program (TPAP), 1974. TPAP, a subdivision of VAP (Visiting Artists Program), gave teachers a source of funding and technical assistance for their own innovative planning.
Music materials, 1973-1977, include records of the Contemporary Music Circuit and the Capitol Concert Series.
Also present are materials related to the 1976 Bicentennial celebration; arts calendars from 1966 to 1978; the Environmental Awareness Project, whose program was to stimulate concern with the physical environment; Executive Director's correspondence from 1966 to 1969; and news clippings from 1962 to 1978.
Arrangement
Arranged into twelve series as follows: 1. "300 Years of Connecticut Architecture" Exhibit, 1968-1974; 2. Dance, 1965-1977; 3. Bicentennial Materials, 1974-1976; 4. Project Create, 1967-1970; 5. Artist-In-Schools Program; 6. Educational Records, 1967-1976; 7. Music, 1973-1977; 8. Arts Calendars, 1973-1977; 9. Environmental Awareness Project, 1969-1970; 10. Internship Program, 1974-1976; Executive Director's Correspondence, 1966-1969; 12. News Clippings, 1962-1978.
Related Material
None.
Index Terms
Organizations:
Connecticut Commission on the Arts
Subjects:
Connecticut Commission on the Arts -- Records and correspondence; Art and state -- Connecticut; Art -- Study and teaching -- Connecticut; Arts -- Connecticut; Performing arts -- Connecticut
Document Types:
Clippings; Correspondence; Press releases; Programs; Reports
Restrictions on Access
These records are stored at an off-site facility and therefore may not be available on a same-day basis.
See the policy.
Provenance
These records were transferred to the State Archives in October 1978 and April 1979.
Container List
- Series 1. "300 Years of Connecticut Architecture" Exhibit, 1968-1974
  - Miscellaneous Pictures and Letters (architecture) (Box 1)
  - Connecticut Society of Architects (Envelope) (Box 1)
  - Houses- 20th Century (Box 1)
  - Honor Award House in November, 1967 November (Box 1)
  - Community Renewal Program, Meriden, CT (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Letters to and from Architects (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Letters to and from Architects Submission form (Box 1)
  - Hartford Survey (Box 1)
  - Groton (Box 1)
  - Center Groton (Box 1)
  - New London (Box 1)
  - Stonington (Box 1)
  - Montville (Box 1)
  - Mystic, Old Mystic (Box 1)
  - Ledyard (Box 1)
  - Waterford-East Lyme (Box 1)
  - Lyme, Old Lyme (Box 1)
  - Tower House, Essex, CT. (Box 1)
  - Hubbard House, Greenwich (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Photographs (Box 1)
  - Pacelle and DeStefano, Architects (Box 1)
  - Pacelle and DeStefano, Architects (Box 1)
  - Pacelle and DeStefano, Architects Miscellaneous Pictures (Box 1)
  - Stamford (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Pictures (Box 1)
  - New Architecture in New Haven (Box 1)
  - New Haven County (Box 1)
  - Bridgeport, Norwalk, Danbury (Box 1)
  - New London (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Pictures and Submission Forms (Box 1)
  - New London (Box 1)
  - New London (Box 1)
  - Hartford (Box 1)
  - Middlesex (Box 1)
  - Farmington (Box 1)
  - Waterbury Area (Box 1)
  - Hartford (Box 1)
  - Middlesex County (Box 1)
  - Hartford (Box 1)
  - Middlesex (Box 1)
  - Philadelphia (Box 1)
  - Windham, Tolland, Hartford County (Box 1)
  - John Fowler (Box 1)
  - New Haven County (Box 1)
  - Manufacturing, 19th Century (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Pictures (Box 1)
  - Commercial, 19th Century (Box 1)
  - Domestic, 19th Century, Federal (Box 1)
  - Houses, 18th Century, detailed (Box 1)
  - Houses, 19th Century, detailed (Box 1)
  - Domestic, 19th Century (Box 1)
  - Domestic, 19th Century, Greek (Box 1)
  - Domestic, 19th Century, Second Empire (Box 1)
  - Domestic, 19th Century, Stick (Box 1)
  - Domestic, 19th Century, Gothic (Box 1)
  - Domestic, 19th Century, Shingle Colonial Period (Box 1)
  - Houses, 18th Century (Box 1)
  - Domestic, 19th Century, Beaux Art (Box 1)
  - Houses, 19th Century (Box 1)
  - Engineering (Box 1)
  - Public, 18th Century (Box 1)
  - Public, 17th Century (Box 1)
  - Collegiate, 20th Century (Box 1)
  - Collegiate, 20th Century (Box 1)
  - Collegiate, 18th Century (Box 1)
  - Public, 19th Century (Box 1)
  - Public, 20th Century (Box 1)
  - Manufacturing, 18th Century (Box 1)
  - Manufacturing, 20th Century (Box 1)
  - Commercial, 20th Century (Box 1)
  - Churches, 20th Century (Box 1)
  - Houses, 17th Century (Box 1)
  - Churches, 18th Century (Box 1)
  - Churches, 19th Century (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives- Box 1 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives- Box 2 (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Negatives- Box 3 (Box 2)
  - Connecticut State Song Composition (Box 2)
  - Mr. Charles L. Fidlar, State Song Coordinator (Box 2)
  - Originals of Letters (Box 2)
  - Form Letters (Box 2)
  - Copyright Information (Box 2)
  - State Song- Competition Guideline (Box 2)
  - Copyright Information (Box 2)
  - Suggestion and Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 2)
  - Answered (Box 2)
  - To Be Answered (Box 2)
  - State Song Composition Guidelines (Box 2)
  - Draft Proposed, G. Hesselberg, 1969 (Box 2)
  - G. Hesselberg under the auspices of CCA (Box 2)
  - Ten Poems by Gregory Hesselberg (Box 2)
  - G. Hesselberg folder (Box 2)
  - G. Hesselberg folder (Box 2)
  - General Operating Procedure (Box 2)
  - G. Hesselberg (Box 2)
  - G. Hesselberg (Box 2)
  - G. Hesselberg (Box 2)
  - 300 Years Advisory Panel Meeting, 1969 October 7 (Box 2)
  - 300 Years Advisory Panel Meeting, 1969 October 7 (Box 2)
  - 300 Years Connecticut Architecture- G. Hesselberg (Box 2)
  - The Palette Magazine of Connecticut Arts Association (Box 2)
  - 300 Years Connecticut Architecture (Box 2)
  - Environmental Meeting, 1969 February 13 (Box 2)
  - Wadsworth Athenaeum (Box 2)
  - G. Hesselberg (Box 2)
  - G. Hesselberg (Box 2)
  - G. Hesselberg (Box 2)
  - Media and Graphics, G. Hasselberg (Box 2)
  - Exhibitions, Designs, Productions and Photos (Box 2)
  - Richard Ellis, Music Planning, Inc. (Box 2)
  - Atty. Peter W. Gillies (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 2)
  - Museum Planning, Inc. (Box 2)
  - Final Photos, 8 x 10 (Box 2)
  - John Zielinski, Contacts (Box 2)
  - New London County, 8 x 10 (include. Mystic Seaport) (Box 2)
  - Middlesex County, 8 x 10 (Dupl. And rejects) (Box 2)
  - Existentialism and Environmental Education (Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 3)
  - Copies of the Report “300 Years of Connecticut Architecture" (Box 3)
  - Richard Ellis- Museum Planning Incorporated (Box 3)
  - News Releases (Box 3)
  - 4 Boxes of Photos (Box 3)
  - Existentialism and Environmental Education (Box 3)
  - Field Trip Schedules and Notes (Box 4)
  - Preservation (Box 4)
  - Editor and Writer (Box 4)
  - Photography (Box 4)
  - Summer Photo Project (Box 4)
  - Sample Text, Chapter 4 (Box 4)
  - Synopsis of Books, Original (Box 4)
  - Materials and Methods, Early Structures (Box 4)
  - Hartford County Survey (Box 4)
  - Middlesex County Survey (Box 4)
  - Litchfield County Survey (Box 4)
  - Middlesex County Survey (Box 4)
  - Mid-State Regional Planning Agency- Middlesex County Architecture (Box 4)
  - Hartford County (Box 4)
  - County - General (Box 4)
  - New London County (Box 4)
  - New Haven County, Research and Documentation (Box 4)
  - New London County, Research and Documentation (Box 4)
  - New Haven County Survey (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 4)
  - Yale Student Project (Box 4)
  - Middlesex County, Research and Documentation (Box 4)
  - Synopsis of Book (Copies) (Box 4)
  - Photography and Research Staff, Orgonschi, Helmbaldt, Le Creier (Box 4)
  - Advisory Panel, Comments of Text (Box 4)
  - Presentation Panels- concepts (Box 4)
  - Connecticut Historical Commission (Box 4)
  - 300 Years, Programs and Objectives (Box 4)
  - Task Force- CSA-AIA (Box 4)
  - Advisory Panel (Box 4)
  - Gregory Hasselberg, G.H., Visual Arts. Comm. (Box 4)
  - Miscellaneous Pictures (Box 4)
  - Public Architecture, Ohio (Box 5)
  - Ohio (Box 5)
  - Public Architecture, Pennsylvania (Box 5)
  - Public Architecture, South Carolina (State Library) (Box 5)
  - Public Architecture, West Virginia (Box 5)
  - Public Architecture, Wisconsin (Box 5)
  - Public Architecture, Virginia (Box 5)
  - Publications- Art in Public Places (Box 5)
  - Title III- Project, Environmental Awareness (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous Environmental Data (Box 5)
  - Architect Selection (Legislation) (Box 5)
  - So. Carolina Architecture, 1670-1970 (Box 5)
  - M. Croman (envelope with pictures- D. Robbins) (Box 5)
  - 300 Years of Architecture- Miscellaneous large pictures (Box 5)
  - The 1967-68 Public Awareness Grant Program- supplement and F-6 Material for your files (Box 5)
  - Environmental Awareness - Lectures, Exhibit and Publications (Box 6)
  - Public Architecture, Survey Cards (Box 6)
  - Public Architecture, Alaska (Box 6)
  - Public Architecture, Alaska (Box 6)
  - Colorado (Box 6)
  - Connecticut (Box 6)
  - Public Architecture, Hawaii (Box 6)
  - Public Architecture, Illinois (Box 6)
  - Public Architecture, Maryland (Box 6)
  - Massachusetts (Box 6)
  - Public Architecture, Nebraska (Box 6)
  - Public Architecture, New Jersey (Box 6)
  - Public Architecture, New York State (Box 6)
  - Public Architecture, North Carolina (Box 6)
  - Pansiera, Dohme and Tilsley, Architects (folder) (Box 6)
  - Connecticut Building Type, Review of Influence and Patterns, 1639-1920 (Box 6)
  - A Homestead Act for Artists (Box 6)
  - New Horizons for Public Buildings (Box 6)
  - 300 Years of Connecticut Architecture - Fact Sheet (Box 6)
  - Commission Meeting- “Public Architecture”, 1970 March 25 (Box 6)
  - Miscellaneous letters (Box 6)
  - Arts/ Bicentennial/ Humanities, Coordinated Public Architecture (Box 6)
  - Minutes on Commission Meeting, 1970 March 25, 27 (Box 6)
  - Connecticut Society of Architects (A.I.A.) (Box 6)
  - Davison Art Center, 1st 50 Years of Lithography (Box 6)
  - Grant Awards (2), 1970 (Box 6)
  - Michael Duffy, Exhibitions (Box 6)
  - Office Exhibitions/ Insurance (Box 6)
  - Housatonic Community College/ Arts Collection (Box 6)
  - Housatonic Community College/ Faculty Exhibition, September 20 - November 14 (Box 6)
  - Individual Artist, References (Box 6)
  - Ad Hoc Legislative Committee (Box 6)
  - Library of Congress - Contract by Correspondence with Sidney Giber (Box 6)
  - Montville - Michael Morris C.D.A.P. Leonard J. Tyl, Supt. Of Schools (Box 6)
  - New Britain Museum of American Art, Exhibition, 1973 June - August (Box 6)
  - Arts for the Capitol (Box 6)
  - Arts for the Capitol (Box 6)
  - State Capitol/ Art Loans (Box 6)
  - Art Loan to Governor’s Residence (Box 6)
  - Davison Art Center, Wesleyan, September, 1973 November (Box 6)
  - Pamphlets - Honor Awards Program, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Arts Center, Assoc. Council of Arts, Florida (Box 6)
  - Columbus Area Chamber of Commerce (Box 6)
- Series 2. Dance, 1965-1977
  - Dance Films (Box 7)
    - Movement Workshop Information (Box 7)
    - Dance Film Library (Box 7)
    - Catalogue of Dance Film (Box 7)
    - Dance films in Connecticut Public Libraries and Information Sheets of Borrowing such from the Library (Box 7)
    - Dance Therapy (Box 7)
    - Book and Film Suggestion (Box 7)
    - Ordered Film (Box 7)
    - Film Usage (Dance collection U-Conn.) (Box 7)
    - Dance Film Showing, 1974 (Box 7)
    - Dance Film Preview, 1971 (Box 7)
    - Dance Film, 1968 September 27-29 (Box 7)
    - Dance Film Comprehensive list submitted (Box 7)
    - Dance Film by Billy Barrow (Box 7)
    - Non-Dance Film List - Library (Box 7)
    - Dance Arts Council Film Folder (Box 7)
  - Dance Companies (Box 7)
    - Connecticut Dance Company (Box 7)
    - AJDE - Folk Ensemble (Box 7)
    - Albana Ballet Academy and Youth Ballet Company (Box 7)
    - Armenian Dance Workshop (Box 7)
    - Artist Collective - Drummers and Dancers (Box 7)
    - Ballet Etudes - Repertory Company (Box 7)
    - Bernhardt Ballet Company (Box 7)
    - Bowen- Peters Dance Company (Box 7)
    - The Center Ballet Theatre (Box 7)
    - Chamber Dance Company (Box 7)
    - Conetic Dance Theatre (Box 7)
    - Confetti Dance Theatre (Box 7)
    - Connecticut Ballet, Inc. (Box 7)
    - Connecticut Dance Theatre (Box 7)
    - Connecticut Valley Regional Ballet Company (Box 7)
    - The consortium (Box 7)
    - Country Dance In Connecticut, Inc. (Box 7)
    - Credo Dancers- Youth Credo Dancers - Jeanne Stair Laeb, N. Woodstock (Box 7)
    - Dance Adventures (Helen Townsend) (Box 7)
    - Dance Alliance of New Haven (Box 8)
    - Dances of Faith (Box 8)
    - Entourage (Box 8)
    - Greater Bridgeport Ballet Company (Box 8)
    - Hartford Ballet Company (Box 8)
    - Hartford Ballet Company (Box 8)
    - Hartford Ballet Company (Box 8)
    - The Hartford Conservatory, Modern Dance Ensemble (Box 8)
    - Kinetikos Dance Company (Box 8)
    - Kathryn Kollar Dance Company (Box 8)
    - Margo Knis Jazz Dance Ensemble (Box 8)
    - New Haven Dance Center Performing Group (Box 8)
    - Nutmeg Ballet Company (Box 8)
    - Pilobolus Dance Theatre (Box 8)
    - Ridgefield Civic Ballet (Box 8)
    - Sonomana Improvisation Dance Theatre (Box 8)
    - Ernestine Stodelle Dance Company (Box 8)
    - College Dance Program (Box 8)
    - Connecticut Colleges - Survey (Box 8)
    - Connecticut Colleges - American Dance Festival (Box 8)
    - Eastern Connecticut State College (Box 8)
    - Quinnipiac College (Box 8)
    - Southern Connecticut State College (Box 8)
    - Trinity College (Judy Divorin) (Box 8)
    - Trinity College (Box 8)
    - University of Bridgeport (Box 8)
    - University of Bridgeport (Box 8)
    - University of Connecticut (Box 8)
    - University of Hartford (Box 8)
    - Wesleyan University (Box 8)
    - Wesleyan university (Box 8)
    - Western Connecticut State College (Box 8)
    - Yale University (Box 8)
    - Empire State Theatre Institute (Box 8)
    - Goddard College (Plainfield, Vermont) (Box 8)
    - New York University (Box 8)
    - New York University Dance Program (Box 8)
    - U-Mass. - Aesthetics and Education (Box 8)
    - Wayne State University (Box 8)
    - University of Wisconsin (Box 8)
    - Assorted News Clippings (Box 8)
    - Newspapers Dance Reviews - articles in Connecticut (Box 8)
    - Press Releases concerning Dance (Box 8)
    - Clippings, Summer, 1970 (Box 8)
    - News Clippings, 1971 (Box 8)
    - News Clippings, 1970 (Box 8)
    - News Clippings, 1971 (Box 8)
    - Pro-Dance, Inc., Director of Dance Teachers, 1973 September (Box 8)
  - Dance Companies Correspondence and Miscellaneous (Box 9)
    - Albano Ballet (Box 9)
    - Ballet Etudes (Box 9)
    - Bowen-Peters Dance (Box 9)
    - Conetic Dance Theatre (Box 9)
    - Chamber Dance Company (Box 9)
    - Connecticut Ballet (Box 9)
    - Connecticut Valley Regional Ballet (Box 9)
    - The Consortium (Box 9)
    - New Haven Dance Alliance (Box 9)
    - Greater Bridgeport Ballet Company (Box 9)
    - Hartford Ballet (Box 9)
    - Hartford Conservatory Modern Dance Ensemble (Box 9)
    - Connecticut Dance Theatre (Box 9)
    - Marge Knis Jazz Dane Company (Box 9)
    - Kathryn Kollar (Box 9)
    - Nutmeg Ballet (Box 9)
    - Scottish Country Dances (Box 9)
    - Ernestine Stodelle Dancers (Box 9)
    - Dance Companies Survey Form (Box 9)
    - Connecticut Dance Companies no longer in existence (Box 9)
    - Ballet Society of Connecticut, Inc. (Box 9)
    - Choreo- Lyric Dance Company (Box 9)
    - New Haven Dance Theatre (Box 9)
    - New England Ballet Theatre (Box 9)
    - New Haven Dance Ensemble (Box 9)
    - New Haven Ballet, Inc. (Box 9)
    - Estelle Jones School of Ballet (Box 9)
    - Foundation Mailing - Info on meetings (Box 9)
    - Transcript of Hearing for members of the Dance Profession, 1967 January 9 (Box 9)
    - Report on the Commission on the Arts (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous Dance Clippings (Box 9)
    - The Dance Quotation Bureau News (Box 9)
    - Articles and Clippings on Dance (Box 9)
    - Action Item (Box 9)
    - Connecticut Colleges offering Dance (Box 9)
    - Connecticut Touring Performers - Dance (Box 9)
    - Connecticut Music, Theatre (Box 9)
    - Evaluation Sheet (Box 9)
    - Dance America (Box 9)
    - Dance Directory (Box 9)
    - Ballet Etuces (Box 9)
    - Bernhard Ballet (Box 9)
    - Bowen-Peters School of dance ($200), 1973, April (Box 9)
    - Albertus Magnus Dance Workshop (Box 9)
    - Confetti Dance Theatre, ($712), 1971/72 (Box 9)
    - Connecticut Ballet Company (formerly New Haven Ballet) (Box 9)
    - Connecticut Valley Regional Ballet (Box 9)
    - Connecticut Valley Regional Ballet - ($1,650), 1973, January (Box 9)
    - Case Study- Dance (Box 9)
    - Studio Commercial teacher summary, 1974 (Box 9)
    - Bicentennial Programming, 1976 (Box 9)
    - Dance Package (Box 9)
    - Dance Teacher Directory (Box 9)
    - Special Project (Box 9)
    - Dance (Box 9)
    - The Feet (Box 9)
    - Licensing of Dance Future (Box 9)
    - Men in Dance (Box 9)
    - Professionalism in Dance (Box 9)
    - Neighborhood Music Schools (Box 9)
    - Publications (Box 9)
    - Bibliography - Dance (Box 9)
    - Bibliography - Movement (Box 9)
    - Dance Book list (Box 9)
    - Stage Nomenclature (Box 9)
    - T.V. (Box 9)
    - Weaving and Movement (Box 9)
    - Funding for the Arts (Box 9)
    - Ethnic Dance (Box 9)
    - Folk Dance (Box 9)
    - Friends of Dance - Lists (Box 9)
    - Michigan Council for the Arts (Box 9)
    - Museum of Contemporary Crafts (Box 9)
    - Stamford Festival of the Arts (Box 9)
    - Dance Company Survey - lists (Box 9)
    - Connecticut Dance Company - Festival Survey (Box 9)
  - Dance Companies, Miscellaneous (Box 10)
    - Connecticut Dance Companies List (Box 10)
    - American Dance Company (Box 10)
    - Association of American Dance Companies (Box 10)
    - Association of American Dance Companies (Box 10)
    - American Dance Festival, Summer, 1974 (Box 10)
    - American Dance Therapy Association (Box 10)
    - American Dance Guild, Inc. (Box 10)
    - American Dance Therapy Association (Box 10)
    - Area Cooperative Educational Services (Box 10)
    - Blue Hills Recreation Association (Box 10)
    - The Bunch, Experimental Theatre - American Dance Festival (Box 10)
    - Bushnell Auditorium (Box 10)
    - Capitol Region Education Council (Box 10)
    - Captain’s Walk, New London (Box 10)
    - Center for Mental Retardation, New York - Medical College, Dance Therapy Course (Box 10)
    - City Center (Box 10)
    - Connecticut Dance Teachers Guild (Box 10)
    - Connecticut Education and School Information, (General) (Box 10)
    - Connecticut Parks and Recreation Conference, 1971, May (Box 10)
    - Ciujahoga Community College, Ohio (Box 10)
    - Cord (C.O.R.D.) (Box 10)
    - Council on Human Services (Box 10)
    - Dance Publication (Box 10)
    - Dance Notation Bureau for Movement Analysis (Box 10)
    - Dancers Studio Foundation, Inc. (Box 10)
    - Early Learning Center, Stamford (Box 10)
    - Educational Center for Human Development (Box 10)
    - Fine Arts Council of Milford (Box 10)
    - Groton Arts Council (Box 10)
    - The Dance Center, Harvard (Box 10)
    - Dance Pedology (Box 10)
    - Impact (Box 10)
    - Joy of Movement Center, Boston (Box 10)
    - Laban Art of Movement Center, London U. (Box 10)
    - Libby Holman Art Center, Stamford (Box 10)
    - Library and Museum of the Performing Arts, Lincoln Center (Box 10)
    - The Loft, Susan Sandel, David Johnson (Box 10)
    - City of Middletown Commission of the Arts (Box 10)
    - National Black Theatre, Barbara Ann Teer (Box 10)
    - National Council of Dance Teacher Organizations (Box 10)
    - National Dance Association (Box 10)
    - New London Arts council (Box 10)
    - Newington Children’s Hospital (Box 10)
    - The Noyes School of Rhythm Foundation, Inc. (Box 10)
    - ORFF Method (Music) Children’s Music (Box 10)